The best way to resist is to survive.
Resistance is a war, history, drama film directed by Jonathan Jakubowicz.
The story of mime Marcel Marceau as he works with a group of Jewish boy scouts and the
French Resistance to save the lives of ten thousand orphans during World War II.
Marcel, played by Jesse Eisenberg.
George S. Patton, played by Ed Harris.
Emma, played by Clémence Poésy.
Klaus Barbie, played by Matthias Schweighöfer.
Elsbeth, played by Bella Ramsey.
Georges Loinger, played by Géza Röhrig.
Resistance is a 2020 biographical drama film written and directed by
Jonathan Jakubowicz, inspired by the life of Marcel Marceau.
It stars Jesse Eisenberg as Marceau, with Clémence Poésy, Matthias Schweighöfer, Alicia von Rittberg, Félix
Moati, Géza Röhrig, Karl Markovics, Vica Kerekes, Bella Ramsey, Ed Harris and Édgar Ramírez.
It was released in the United States on March 27, 2020, by IFC Films.
Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, only a few independent and drive-in theaters remained open, and so
Resistance topped the weekend box office in its opening weekend by earning $2,490 on one screen.
The film explores themes of resistance, world war ii,
based on true story, gestapo, french gestapo.
The tone is emotional.